// Environmental Questions
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Name the atmospheric layer closest to the ground",
    answer: "Troposphere",
    options: [
      "Troposphere",
      "Mesosphere",
      "Thermosphere",
      "Stratosphere"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The most abundant gas on the earth’s atmosphere is",
    answer: "Nitrogen",
    options: [
      "Oxygen",
      "Carbon",
      "Nitrogen",
      "Hydrogen"

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What atmospheric layer has most of the clouds?",
    answer: "Troposphere",
    options: [
      "Thermosphere",
      "Mesosphere",
      "Exosphere",
      "Troposphere"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The study of weather is called?",
    answer: "meteorology",
    options: [
      "meteorology",
      "climatology",
      "aeronomy",
      "aerology"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which one of the following is NOT a primary layer of the atmosphere?",
    answer: "Exosphere",
    options: [
      "Mesosphere",
      "Troposphere",
      "Exosphere",
      "Stratosphere"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "Name the atmospheric layer that is completely cloudless and free of water vapor.",
  answer: "Thermosphere",
  options: [
    "Exosphere",
    "Troposphere",
    "Thermosphere",
    "Stratosphere"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "The ozone layer or ozone shield is a region of Earth’s atmosphere that absorbs most of the Sun’s ultraviolet (UV) radiation. Which layer of the atmosphere contains ozone layer?",
  answer: "Stratosphere",
  options: [
    "Troposphere",
    "Mesosphere",
    "Thermosphere",
    "Stratosphere"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "What is the average atmospheric pressure at sea level as defined by the International Standard Atmosphere?",
  answer: "101325 pascals",
  options: [
    "101325 pascals",
    "14.6959 pascals",
    "1013 pascals",
    "984.43 pascals"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "The major diet of pandas is",
  answer: "Bamboo",
  options: [
    "Acacia leave",
    "Bamboo",
    "Grass",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "Which of the following is an amphibian?",
  answer: "Salamanders",
  options: [
    "Salamanders",
    "Lizards",
    "Fish",
    "None of these"
  ]
},

];
